{
    "subject": "resource/Suricata_(software)",
    "predicate": "ontology/license",
    "object": "resource/GNU_General_Public_License",
    "human_readable": "The license of Suricata (software) is GNU General Public License.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9371143579483032,
            "question": "What does the GNU General Public License allow users to do with Suricata?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8996925950050354,
            "question": "Does the GNU General Public License require attribution for modifications to Suricata?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8976017236709595,
            "question": "How does the GNU General Public License impact the development of Suricata?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8955861330032349,
            "question": "What kind of software license is the GNU General Public License?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7703261971473694,
            "question": "What is the license of Suricata?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5736319422721863,
            "question": "Is Suricata open-source software?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5208789706230164,
            "question": "Under which license can Suricata be used and modified?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4650118947029114,
            "question": "Are there any restrictions on distributing Suricata under its current license?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3215814232826233,
            "question": "Can commercial entities use Suricata?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31946688890457153,
            "question": "What are the terms and conditions associated with using Suricata?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The license of Suricata (software) is GNU General Public License.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7738_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can commercial entities use Suricata?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7738_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any restrictions on distributing Suricata under its current license?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7738_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Under which license can Suricata be used and modified?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7738_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7738_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7738_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7738_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7738_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7738_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7738_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7738_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7738_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7738_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7738_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information clearly states, \"Suricata source code is licensed under version 2 of the GNU General Public License,\" which supports the provided statement that the license for Suricata (software) is the GNU General Public License."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}